<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TEA Mobile IDE</string>
    <string name="powered_by">This technology is brought to you by Nuchwezi Research.
        \n\nTEA (Transforming Executable Alphabet) computer programming language is a new modern general-purpose programming language being developed by Joseph Willrich Lutalo C.M.R.W.
        \n\nSO HOW COULD IT HELP YOU?
        \n\nSolving Arbitrary problems in your domain, business or study area using programming skills.
        \n\nIn a world where many problems can be modelled using mathematics, logic and text-processing, the TEA language offers one of the simplest methods to get started prototyping a solution that works.
        \n\nThis TEA MOBILE IDE is an echo of the earlier TEA WEB IDE, and is meant to extend the access and usability of TEA to those working while on the move, those working OFFLINE and those who wish to carry their work even into bed!
        \n\n------- HIGHLIGHTS -------
        \n\n1. Even though still experimental, the MOBILE TEA experience almost is at par with that of using TEA on the WEB or the Linux commandline (in some ways, even better!)
        \n\n2. The same TEA skills used on WEB and CLI likewise apply here. So, leverage the same documentation and skills.
        \n\n3. This App allows you to fetch the TEA STANDARD programs from the latest sources online, and stores them for later (OFFLINE) use.
        \n\n4. Just like with WEB TEA, you can write your program at your own pace, test and return to it any time. The IDE always keeps you latest work loaded even when the app is closed accidentally, or that it crashes and you need to restart/resume later.
        \n\n5. Once your TEA program produces/outputs results, you have the option to copy them into the clipboard so as to share them/export them out of the app to your other apps or even into social media or your research work...
        \n\n------- OTHER TIPS -------
         \n\nYou can assign names to your TEA programs, and use the \'SAVE\' feature to store them, with even multiple versions assigned names based on most recent. You can reload any of these saved programs later, and update or run/test them. But can also delete.
    \n\nCOPYRIGHT &amp; LEGAL
    \n\n&#169; Nuchwezi (nuchwezi.com) | REPORT ERRORS+BUGS: tech@nuchwezi.com
    </string>
</resources>